[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Captain Edward J. Smith was captain of Titanic. Who was the first officer?", "correct_answer": "William McMaster Murdoch", "incorrect_answers": ["Archibald Butt", "Benjamin Guggenheim", "John Jacob Astor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the U.S., the maximum term of an issued patent is this many years, from the earliest claimed filing date.", "correct_answer": "20", "incorrect_answers": ["17", "7", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was Dan Dreidberg the first Nite Owl in the Watchmen?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about ticks, common ectoparasites and vectors of numerous diseases?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They feed on blood.", "Young ticks have 6 legs, and mature ticks have 8 legs.", "They live on mammals, birds, reptiles and amphibians."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedy, based on the life experiences of Rodney Ansell, won an Academy Award and three Golden Globes and spawned two sequels.", "correct_answer": "Crocodile Dundee", "incorrect_answers": ["The Secret of My Success", "Beverly Hills Cop", "48 Hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Periplaneta americana, Blattella germanica and Gromphadorhina portentosa are all species of this insect.", "correct_answer": "Cockroach", "incorrect_answers": ["House fly", "Stick Insect", "Butterfly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used by skiers to describe wet granular snow?", "correct_answer": "Corn", "incorrect_answers": ["Goobers", "Clumps", "Snow peas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Valley Girl, what color do Julie and Tommy wear to the prom?", "correct_answer": "Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Baby blue", "Red", "Yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only US state famous for producing limburger cheese in the Chalet Cheese Co-op factory?", "correct_answer": "Wisconsin", "incorrect_answers": ["Minnessota", "New York", "Ohio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played the role of Mr. Rooney, the high school principal, in the 1986 comedy Ferris Buellers Day Off?", "correct_answer": "Jeffery Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Sheen", "Matthew Broderick", "Alan Ruck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what 1942 movie is the line Louis, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship?", "correct_answer": "Casablanca", "incorrect_answers": ["Citizen Kane", "Sunset Boulevard", "On the Waterfront"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who played Duckie in the 1986 film Pretty in Pink also starred in what popular CBS sitcom, which began airing in 2003?", "correct_answer": "Two and a Half Men", "incorrect_answers": ["King of Queens", "How I Met Your Mother", "The Office"]}]